#### **Iherrera**

Cryptocurrency privacy-focused Monero (XMR) enthusiast. Focused in open-source software GNU/Linux operating systems since 2016.

Studied Software Engineering foundations at Holberton School Colombia with a high passion for blockchain technology.

I'm an entrepreneur and an adventurer eager to build the present. Software engineer with experience in C and Python, HTML, CSS, and MySQL/PostgreSQL relational databases.

### Experience

# **SUPPORT ENGINEER | Dec 2021 to Current Addi - Colombia**

- Customer technical support: resolve CX (customer experience team) requests, automated workflows, user flow, and app issues, analyze technical client logs, error detection, request escalation, and training.
- Engineering Support: request escalation, detect/open incidents (analiyze impact), share logs, stats.
- Engineering projects: Python scripting, automated jobs.

Software Tooling: Slack, DBeaver (PostgreSQL), Kustomer, LogRocket (app visual log sessions), Grafana (Loki - log analyzer; schedule handler, incident management system), Databricks (automated cluster management; graphical command-line interface), Sublime (IDE), Python (Pycharm), Notion (documentation), Asana (task management), Lucidchart (diagrams).

Development: SCRUM (sprints)

# COMMUNICATION WORK-GROUP COORDINATOR | Jul 2018 to Nov 2021 Monero - Global (Colombia)

- Workgroup communication coordinator
- Project task management coordinator
- Junior IT

# **SOFTWARE ENGINEER | Sep 2020 to Sep 2021 Blockchain Labb - UK**

- Development Coordinator (Team Lead): organize and coordinate development working directly with the developers to follow the company's needs and blockchain integrations.
- Code Reviewer (QA): check the developer's code.
- Repository and Server Maintainer: maintain, review, and check repository's commits and accept changes.
- IT: SysOps/DevOps server maintainer.
- Programming Languages: Vuejs, Nuxtjs, Nodejs.

#### DATABASE ANALYST | Sep 2016 to Feb 2018 Emcali - Telecomunicaciones - Valle del Cauca, Colombia

- Database Analyst: Microsoft Excel
- GIS (Geographic Information System) Analyst: GEOVISOR/MapInfo software
- Recruiter: assistant training

- Software: OPEN-SmartFlex utility software

### BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT ADMINISTRATOR | Feb 2013 to May 2016 Productos Vrinda - Colombia

Production and service manager. Responsibilities included customer service area, staff planning,

purchase, storage, and sales. Contact suppliers, financial accounting control, resource optimization, and compliance with quality standards and regulations of the food and beverage sector.

# **GEOREFERENCER** | Feb 2010 to Feb 2013 Servinformación S.A. - Colombia

Homologate national property number in the company's databases to the EMCALI subscriber. Routing

fieldwork through Geographic Information Systems (GIS). Geographic software layer control, collector

supervisor, and coordinate localization updates.

#### Skills

Python (Programming Language) • Support Engineering • PostgreSQL

#### Education

- HOLBERTON SCHOOL: SOFTWARE ENGINEER, PROGRAMMING · (2019 2021)
- UDEMY ACADEMY: WEB DESIGNER, WEB DEVELOPMENT (2017 2018)
- UNIVERSIDAD LIBRE SECCIONAL CALI: ECONOMICS, ECONOMY · (2006 2017)

### Certifications

Software Engineering: Implementation and Testing Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python) Python Data Structures EF SET English Certificate 94/100 (C1 Advanced) EF SET Certificate

### Languages

Español (Native or Bilingual) Inglés (high proeficient - C1)